<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Kevin's Blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[A personal development blog.]]></description><link>https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/kevinsblog</link><image><url>https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/kevinsblog/logos/logo-512.png</url><title>Kevin&apos;s Blog</title><link>https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/kevinsblog</link></image><generator>GatsbyJS Material Starter</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 18:21:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/kevinsblog/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><author><![CDATA[Kevin Mongiello]]></author><copyright><![CDATA[Copyright © 2018. Kevin Mongiello]]></copyright><item><title><![CDATA[What skills should I be working on?]]></title><description><![CDATA[How do I want/intend to live my life?  I intend to live my life
comfortably, pleasurably, motivated by love, and doing things that
give me…]]></description><link>https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/kevinsblog/what-skills-should-i-be-working-on</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/kevinsblog/what-skills-should-i-be-working-on</guid><category><![CDATA[Reflections]]></category><category><![CDATA[Growth]]></category><category><![CDATA[Earth Star]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Mongiello]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;How do I want/intend to live my life?  I intend to live my life
comfortably, pleasurably, motivated by love, and doing things that
give me satisfaction.  Living from a beautiful, bountiful, abundant state of mind.
I like feeling complete.  There are areas of my life that I feel are not complete.
I find pleasure and fulfillment from working towards completion.  I recognize
an impulsiveness that can often take away/distract me from completion.  I also notice
food/taking snack breaks as a method/manifestation of this tendancy.  When I get
close or have the opportunity to be with my self, the best thing I can do is to sit with, listen to,
reflect on, write about, and/or learn from whatever is here.  I have been feeling incomplete &amp;#x26; detached
because I have not been spending time with my self when the perfect opportunities arise.
I am the keys to my own success, I am the answers to all the seemingly tough questions.  I am the roadmap through life&apos;s
journey. I am exactly what I want, and the best skill to be improving is being me;
following my dreams, my passions, my interests, my truths, and my desires.  Everything else is an illusion.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking Inventory]]></title><description><![CDATA[  Easy to read. (Entertaining)
  Clear and Deliberate. (Meaningful)
  Short and sweet. (Concise) Shortest and sweetest
I quit my job to make…]]></description><link>https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/kevinsblog/taking-inventory</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/kevinsblog/taking-inventory</guid><category><![CDATA[Reflections]]></category><category><![CDATA[Growth]]></category><category><![CDATA[Earth Star]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Mongiello]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;  Easy to read. (Entertaining)
Clear and Deliberate. (Meaningful)
Short and sweet. (Concise)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shortest and sweetest
I quit my job to make more space for myself.  I&apos;ve been taking some time off to
hit the reset button. For almost 99% of my life, I&apos;ve been living in my head
dreaming of things that are outside of me.
The present moment is all there is, and living outside of it is equivalent to losing touch with reality.
Reality is here, and it is now, and for most of my life I have been living there and then.
Living in the there and then, lots of negative things come to the surface as a result of
being detached from myself. For a long time it&apos;s perplexed me,
because it&apos;s hard for me to even determine what &quot;myself&quot; is.
It seems like such an etheric, mysterious essence that is always morphing and remolding to take
the shape of whatever beliefs I&apos;m establishing or new routine I&apos;m experimenting with.
Ultimately I am consciousness.  I am witnessing a gentle stroke of a beard.
I am aware of a desire to make an awesome blog post.  I am aware of anxiety
that comes from committing to certain words phrases and paragraphs versus others.
I&apos;m coming to realize, that I am just the observer, the experiencer of all the things
that take place in my life.  For so long it&apos;s been impossible for me to describe myelf,
because all the events and things which people usually use to describe themselves are always
changing and evolving for me.  The way in which I live life now is drastically different from the
way I lived it 5 years ago.
My preferences, eating habits, workout routines, daily activities all either modified, refined, or completely different.
There&apos;s no certainty that I can say how the next 5 years will differ either.  So,
when it comes for me to describe myself, it&apos;s like trying to draw a portrait
of an ameoba that is constantly changing size and shape and orientation.  It&apos;s actually
quite beautiful now that am blessed to be recognizing what it is.  I am not the events
that take up my time, I am not the awards and merits I receive for my actions,
I am not a bunch of lines on a resume.  I am a soul feeling consciousness through a body, and
I experience sensations and emotions.  It sounds so over-simplified, yet when I
try to coerce myself into being something more than that, I lose myself to some
illustration of what I think life should look and who I want to be in 20 years,
and what I think a future employer will see in me and the list goes on... and I fall out of touch with all
myself... I fall out of touch with this illusive, magical, mystery essence that is
rooted deeply into the ancient source of life.  It&apos;s still a little mind-boggling
how &quot;I&quot; can be out of touch with &quot;myself&quot;.  Are they two separate things?
Who knows, the mind can&apos;t keep up with the spirit.  I&apos;m afraid that all of this
will be too much spiritual jargon, but then again I&apos;m not even sure who my audience is yet.
I am happy to be writing words and taking a step in life in a direction that is calling me.
The direction is inward, and this blog is a record of my efforts and revelations
while discovering the parts of me that have always been there but have not gotten
the attention they deserved.  I am going to do less, feel more, and then be, in that order.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&apos;s certain something about taking a full 60-ish seconds to go from 0 to 40 mph on the
roads late at night in my hometown that makes me feel a certain freedom which opens
me up to a fulfilling breath and a cool sense of relxation.  Knowing that I don&apos;t have
anywhere to be other than right here, right now.  And that I&apos;ll be exactly no different
when I get to my destination, so what&apos;s the rush?  When I&apos;m totally comfortable in my own self
then there really is no rush to do anything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may be wondering what the heck &quot;Earth Star&quot; is. That&apos;s quite okay - I almost am too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earth Star is a project where I gather up my ego, my pride, my fear, my shame,
and all limiting beliefs and put them on the side lines, render them useless, and let
something much more powerful than me take the stage.  In my humble opinion,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;step aside as an ego, Earth Star is a power greater than me that is asking to come through and make an impact here.
I have no idea how, or what Earth Star will accomplish during my life.
I just know that I&apos;m supposed to settle my ego, step aside for Earth Star
to come through me, and find out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe the essence of Earth Star is community based; a place where the seeking soul can find refugee and be part of a
bigger picture where souls empower one another.  My ego is scared, because I feel like
I&apos;m trying to conquer such a big task without any real clear roadmap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just know that it will happen or I&apos;ll die trying. I really have no other options.
Every other road that I continue down is just as empty as the next and leaves me unfulfilled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Patience.  I&apos;m learning to step out of the way so that my soul can shine through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve always wanted to record my life.  I feel like the documentation will be interesting
to read in retrospect.  Things that seem like big life crises&apos; right now, will not seem
so magnanimous when looking back.  Or maybe the events right now will be some unimaginable turning
point that pivots my life towards great success, or who knows, great failure!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything is so beautiful when life gets calm and quiet.  I am working on cultivating
more of that beauty in my life so that I can operate from that space.  I have been living
with this feeling that&apos;s been buried deep in my heart, and it comes alive during beautiful moments.
I feel I am supposed to share it with the world. I have had a lot of trouble sitting here
trying to figure out what I&apos;m supposed to say I&apos;m doing with myself since I quit.
The honest truth is, a lot of times I really don&apos;t know, but that is only half of the story.
The other half, is that I&apos;m unveiling a deeper part of myself that has all the answers.
Half of me is scared, because that half has no answers and feels like I&apos;m walking into the dark,
taking a leap into the unknown.  But the more and more I cultivate a healthy relationship
with the part of me that is eternal, the stronger my trust grows and I know that I&apos;m stepping
into ownership of a power that I&apos;m born with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel scared not having a job and knowing that my gap of employement is widening with each moment.
I often feel pressure to crank up the heat and figure out what is going to be my next move and
how I&apos;m going to stay afloat.
I&apos;ve always been a risk taker though, and my intuition is backing me on this 100%.  Sometimes my mind
gets in the way and starts going haywyre and all the feelings I&apos;m supposed to be conquering
come flooding back in, telling me that I haven&apos;t achieved anything and that this whole experiment
has been a huge mistake!... But the thing is, I have gotten better. and so even though those feelings are as pervasive as ever,
I have a much deeper awareness of what&apos;s going on my body (and my head) and
and has been telling me
to rewrite the rules of life since almost forever, I feel like there is no better time than right now
to
I quit my job to deal with the stress of being alive, and then having no job introduced
anxiety related stress, and overall I&apos;m still not
It&apos;s taken a lot of work, and I&apos;m still nowhere near masterhood. However, I am confident
that this road will bring me&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve been taking time to really ground myself into my true self by deepening my
awareness and emotional intelligence and rekindling a long-overdue relationship with
myself.  I have pushed myself to the side for quite some time and finally I am
making amends to live from a place that honors the soft, compassionate, loving side
and also the goal oriented, action-taking side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started reading OSHO, whom I value highly, because he speaks of beautiful things in a way that
feel like they are coming straight from my own heart.  I used to feel isolated from others,
because I feel like I see the world in such a deep way that is underneath how people act,
how society functions, etc.  I never had a deep enough understanding and enough experience
to express those topics to others whom I wasn&apos;t sure could see the same way as me, and so I felt
as if I was very isolated in a box made different than others. The topics are very metaphysical yet
OSHO magnificently portrays such timeless and arcane topics in an easy digestible way with an anecdote to guide every message.
When I read OSHO I truly feel like finally I know someone who I share a common experience of reality with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started going deep into my own emotions and giving myself the ability to truly witness and feel
what is inside of me.  Once I can truly witness and allow myself to feel what is there, the feelings pass
almost immediately.  The trick is to be able and willing to go deep enough to fully see what has been hidden in darkness.
I have a history of pushing my feelings aside, because I did not have the tools or training to process and understand them,
and because they are painful!  But neglecting pain may work as a temporary escape, but wounds won&apos;t heal until
the healing process has begun, and if I tell myself to look away, to ignore the pain, then I will never focus any
healing powers on it.
I have been using tools such as Emotional Freedom Technique (EFT or &quot;tapping&quot;) to
gain deeper insight into my inner emotional and energetic workings. This is the root of all depression, I believe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know deep down but did not have the understanding to communicate  exercises that&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I quit my job.  I was devoting my life to something that didn&apos;t fulfill me and
was spiritually draining me.  On top of that, I&apos;ve been challenged with depression,
stress, anxiety, and more; all of which I refuse to take medication for.  I made a habit of burying all of those
things in order to stay on track long enough to reach the next checkpoint on a life that never truly belonged to me.
Staying focused on targets ahead of us is a good way to forget about the pain we are in,
but eventually you need to slow down and take some rest, and things have a way of catching up to us.
I was building life from the template of some ideal vision, I was very disconnected to who I am.
Who I am doesn&apos;t care about working a job just for money and experience.  Who I am
needs to have a strong daily meditation practice
My creativity was dying, and with the pressure to keep up at work, I felt like I could either
barely keep afloat at a work environment that was stripping me from the things that matter in life,
or I could take a plunge into foreign, unknown waters that seemed to be calling me.
I decided to take the plunge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ultimately I have been missing myself.  I&apos;ve been separated from myself
A lot of things have happened internally since then.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is scary to build life from scratch all on your own, and it&apos;s safer to borrow what has &quot;worked&quot; for other people.
Go to school, get a job, buy a house, start a family, etc.  But that path was just sooooo not what I wanted.
In building someone elses version of life, I was ignoring the things most fundamental to me which were causing my
emotional-psychological ailments. So, I realized that money and job security isn&apos;t worth sacrificing
self-realization, and liberation of my soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; In many ways I am deeply grateful for
the opportunity to work there and everything that I was able to learn from the team and the experience.  However
good it looked on paper, the top-dollar I earned and the personal sacrificies I made working on a project I wasn&apos;t passionate
about didn&apos;t help cure any of my deeper ails and only left me wanting more and feeling emptier than ever.
I know deep down that I am everything I&apos;ve been looking for, and the road that I was on
was not fulfilling my basic needs of getting me closer to my ultimate goals.  While
it looked great on paper, and people around me may think I&apos;m crazy, I&apos;m happy that I left my
high-paying job and took time off to do some good earnest soul-searching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;id-like-to-explain&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#id-like-to-explain&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;anchor&quot;&gt;&lt;svg aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot; height=&quot;16&quot; version=&quot;1.1&quot; viewBox=&quot;0 0 16 16&quot; width=&quot;16&quot;&gt;&lt;path fill-rule=&quot;evenodd&quot; d=&quot;M4 9h1v1H4c-1.5 0-3-1.69-3-3.5S2.55 3 4 3h4c1.45 0 3 1.69 3 3.5 0 1.41-.91 2.72-2 3.25V8.59c.58-.45 1-1.27 1-2.09C10 5.22 8.98 4 8 4H4c-.98 0-2 1.22-2 2.5S3 9 4 9zm9-3h-1v1h1c1 0 2 1.22 2 2.5S13.98 12 13 12H9c-.98 0-2-1.22-2-2.5 0-.83.42-1.64 1-2.09V6.25c-1.09.53-2 1.84-2 3.25C6 11.31 7.55 13 9 13h4c1.45 0 3-1.69 3-3.5S14.5 6 13 6z&quot;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;I&apos;d like to explain&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I quit my job.  January 3rd, 2018, I left my high-paying job at a fast-paced startup called CaliberMind (CM).  Even though
it was a dream come true and serendipitous beyond belief that we crossed paths, leaving was meant to be, and I&apos;m not looking back
(Technically I got laid off, but I was literally going to quit the same exact day... seriously).
Working at CM was a huge committment and I ended up working far over 40 hours nearly every week.
I enjoyed a lot of my time at CM, and the skills and experience that I gained from
the project and the team is invaluable to me.  However, I kept feeling like there was
greater work to be done elsewhere.  This feeling was very persistent, and eventually it
bubbled up from the tiny, hardly visibile depths of my being to the top level where
it practicaly began overflowing into every aspect of my existence. I told my boss I wasn&apos;t feeling
so hot about the project anymore, and we decided I ought to take some time to reflect and make a decision.
Another 2 weeks went by, and It was telling me, for one thing, to quit my job.  I didn&apos;t know
where it would lead me if I gave into it, but I couldn&apos;t ignore it plus I&apos;m
an evangelist for following intuition. I went into work with a firm decision to quit that day,
and I ended up leaving laid off instead.  So, I still say I quit.  After all, it was my
energy that made the decision for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fast forward 5 months and some change later, and I&apos;m sitting behind my laptop in my old bedroom at my parents&apos;
house in New Jersey writing this blog post and I could not be any more grateful for the way life has unfolded since.
I have come to know that part inside of me that was begging me to quit and I&apos;m starting to feel whole again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a part of me that had been tugging on my sleeves telling me to pay attention to it&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think we&apos;ve grown up in a society that makes it easy to forget ourselves and instead adopt
the standards of someone else&apos;s ideal life.  For example, Everyone has this idea that they are
supposed to go graduate highschool, get a degree in something, find a &quot;real&quot; job, have a family,
get a loan from the bank to buy a house that takes 20+ years to pay off, and that&apos;s what happiness looks like.  Right?
Well that may be somebodies ideal, and it may be what a lot of people think is their ideal, but we all have heard of
mid-life crises&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the past months I&apos;ve been traveling,
reflecting, suffering in emotional and physical pain, growing wild like bamboo, and trimming myself back like a fresh haircut.
I&apos;ve been depressed, elated, lethargic, ecstatic, determined, lackluster, and everything inbetween.  Overall, the focus has always been on me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know I&apos;m here on Earth for a reason, and that reason is to kick ass!!!... Well, no, but actually kind of yes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My purpose is to share with the world something that can&apos;t exactly be explained in words
but can definitely be shown by the actions and creations that spawn from it.  It&apos;s sort of like an essence,
and I consider myself a major shareholder of this primordial, thriving, high-energy... stuff.
Let me be pessimistic for a second: For the most part, people are using tiny percentages of their potential.  A lot of the
things that hold us back are
In my opinion, I think it&apos;s somethings that more people ought to get to know, so I&apos;m making it my mission
to take a hold of it and show it to the world.  I&apos;m not the first to do it, but the more the merrier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;a-new-chapter&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#a-new-chapter&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;anchor&quot;&gt;&lt;svg aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot; height=&quot;16&quot; version=&quot;1.1&quot; viewBox=&quot;0 0 16 16&quot; width=&quot;16&quot;&gt;&lt;path fill-rule=&quot;evenodd&quot; d=&quot;M4 9h1v1H4c-1.5 0-3-1.69-3-3.5S2.55 3 4 3h4c1.45 0 3 1.69 3 3.5 0 1.41-.91 2.72-2 3.25V8.59c.58-.45 1-1.27 1-2.09C10 5.22 8.98 4 8 4H4c-.98 0-2 1.22-2 2.5S3 9 4 9zm9-3h-1v1h1c1 0 2 1.22 2 2.5S13.98 12 13 12H9c-.98 0-2-1.22-2-2.5 0-.83.42-1.64 1-2.09V6.25c-1.09.53-2 1.84-2 3.25C6 11.31 7.55 13 9 13h4c1.45 0 3-1.69 3-3.5S14.5 6 13 6z&quot;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;A new chapter&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-mountain-behind&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#the-mountain-behind&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;anchor&quot;&gt;&lt;svg aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot; height=&quot;16&quot; version=&quot;1.1&quot; viewBox=&quot;0 0 16 16&quot; width=&quot;16&quot;&gt;&lt;path fill-rule=&quot;evenodd&quot; d=&quot;M4 9h1v1H4c-1.5 0-3-1.69-3-3.5S2.55 3 4 3h4c1.45 0 3 1.69 3 3.5 0 1.41-.91 2.72-2 3.25V8.59c.58-.45 1-1.27 1-2.09C10 5.22 8.98 4 8 4H4c-.98 0-2 1.22-2 2.5S3 9 4 9zm9-3h-1v1h1c1 0 2 1.22 2 2.5S13.98 12 13 12H9c-.98 0-2-1.22-2-2.5 0-.83.42-1.64 1-2.09V6.25c-1.09.53-2 1.84-2 3.25C6 11.31 7.55 13 9 13h4c1.45 0 3-1.69 3-3.5S14.5 6 13 6z&quot;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;The Mountain Behind&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mountain has a lot of perks.  It is away from civilization and still embodies
a pure form of nature that is yet to be affected by humanities modern ways. Peaceful
as it is, it lacks one thing essential to humans - humanity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve spent a lot of time working on the machine under my hood.  Working through
old emotions that I have never observed and honored and thus never put to rest.
I&apos;ve been discovering patterns and limiting beliefs that affect my every day life
and mood.  I&apos;ve also been using this time to properly come to terms with the
reality of our civilization at this point in time. Whether it be the climate,
politics, the downside of technology, entitlement in Western culture, the
perspective that I carry is very powerful, for better or worse.  It can be a
sabateur, casting shadows of fear around every corner, or it can uplift and
inspire and motivate to move forward.  We all have the power to choose our
beliefs, yet sometimes they have been with us so long and are rooted so deeply
that we are not conscious of where our thoughts, tendencies, and outlook are
stemming from.  Through meditation, stillness, insight from peers and mentors
it is possible to gain a more objective analysis of what is driving the car of
our lives - our consciousness, or our unconscious patterns and conditionings.
It can be a slow and painful process to take these learnings and reshape life to a
different mold, and in order to embody the me I see at the top of all my potential,
I have deemed it a necessary endeavor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On paper, it is hard to explain without a long and philosophical explanation, and it may seem like no progress has been made
in my life after leaving my job. However, I am confident I will look back on this period of time knowing just how critical
the advancements made were.  I am now fully equipped to balance my life, transmute negative emotions,
sustain rigorous yet healthy schedules, and live in a way that fully keeps my spirit high even under high work loads.
I deem it as a fresh upgrade to an old outdated Operating System.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is still a lot of work to be done, and the work is neverending.  To stay
in the mountains of my life - isolated, hermetic, withdrawn - is to give up many
of the things that make life so enjoyable.  I find my greatest pleasure and most
joy when actively pursuing tangible goals and working towards making dreams a reality.
Sure, the time spent optimizing myself plays an important role in accelerating &amp;#x26;
fulfilling my dreams. However, I feel called to start showing back up in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-road-ahead&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#the-road-ahead&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;anchor&quot;&gt;&lt;svg aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot; height=&quot;16&quot; version=&quot;1.1&quot; viewBox=&quot;0 0 16 16&quot; width=&quot;16&quot;&gt;&lt;path fill-rule=&quot;evenodd&quot; d=&quot;M4 9h1v1H4c-1.5 0-3-1.69-3-3.5S2.55 3 4 3h4c1.45 0 3 1.69 3 3.5 0 1.41-.91 2.72-2 3.25V8.59c.58-.45 1-1.27 1-2.09C10 5.22 8.98 4 8 4H4c-.98 0-2 1.22-2 2.5S3 9 4 9zm9-3h-1v1h1c1 0 2 1.22 2 2.5S13.98 12 13 12H9c-.98 0-2-1.22-2-2.5 0-.83.42-1.64 1-2.09V6.25c-1.09.53-2 1.84-2 3.25C6 11.31 7.55 13 9 13h4c1.45 0 3-1.69 3-3.5S14.5 6 13 6z&quot;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;The Road Ahead&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will start devoting more of my time to projects.  I will still grow
the self-mastery practices I have been developing while in the mountains.  Now, it will
take a new shape as I balance it the work I choose to move forward with in other realms.
I also will be making time to serve others, as I think this is the single greatest
thing that can be performed while on Earth.  Like my Tai Chi Master Ann Wheeler says,
&quot;If it&apos;s not good for other people, or it&apos;s not good for the Earth, then it&apos;s not good for anybody!&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;welcome-change&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#welcome-change&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;anchor&quot;&gt;&lt;svg aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot; height=&quot;16&quot; version=&quot;1.1&quot; viewBox=&quot;0 0 16 16&quot; width=&quot;16&quot;&gt;&lt;path fill-rule=&quot;evenodd&quot; d=&quot;M4 9h1v1H4c-1.5 0-3-1.69-3-3.5S2.55 3 4 3h4c1.45 0 3 1.69 3 3.5 0 1.41-.91 2.72-2 3.25V8.59c.58-.45 1-1.27 1-2.09C10 5.22 8.98 4 8 4H4c-.98 0-2 1.22-2 2.5S3 9 4 9zm9-3h-1v1h1c1 0 2 1.22 2 2.5S13.98 12 13 12H9c-.98 0-2-1.22-2-2.5 0-.83.42-1.64 1-2.09V6.25c-1.09.53-2 1.84-2 3.25C6 11.31 7.55 13 9 13h4c1.45 0 3-1.69 3-3.5S14.5 6 13 6z&quot;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Welcome Change&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m thinking of getting a new job. I&apos;ve already begun testing the waters and
sending out applications.  I&apos;ve been pondering the idea of starting my own business
for a while, because I really want to be my own boss and shape the world in a way
that I see best fit.  However, I have been getting home-sick by not having a place
to truly settle into and call my own.  I want to furnish a place, coordinate
ambiences for rooms, and decorate according to my inner guidance.  I guess I could
do that in the places I&apos;ve been staying temporarily, but they are simply just
temporary residences.  The morale of the story is that I&apos;m thinking of getting a
job to support me moving out into a place of my own.  While this feels like it could
thwart my momentum into brainstorming &amp;#x26; developing my own business, I also am more
tolerant of the feelings of doubt and fear that question if it is the right decision.
Ultimately, I can quit a job just as quickly as I get one (or probably even quicker), and
so any fear that I feel about getting a job is really just fear of getting stuck
in a job that I don&apos;t want.  Since I&apos;m the master of my reality, and I have trust
in my path, I release any fear, knowing that I am in complete control.  This is nothing
but movement.  I tend to do best when I keep myself moving.  And I&apos;m getting the calling.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>