<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Kevin's Blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[A personal development blog.]]></description><link>https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog</link><image><url>https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/logos/logo-512.png</url><title>Kevin&apos;s Blog</title><link>https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog</link></image><generator>GatsbyJS Material Starter</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 03:18:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><author><![CDATA[Kevin Mongiello]]></author><copyright><![CDATA[Copyright © 2018. Kevin Mongiello]]></copyright><item><title><![CDATA[Master Consciousness]]></title><description><![CDATA[I want to master my consciousness... I will be the master of consciousness... No... I will live and operate from master consciousness. I…]]></description><link>https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/master-consciousness</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/master-consciousness</guid><category><![CDATA[Purpose]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Mongiello]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I want to master my consciousness...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be the master of consciousness...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No... I will live and operate from master consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recognize the ego that wants and chooses based on thoughts and emotions.  I also recognize a part of me
that is beyond thought and emotion.  It always can be heard but is seldom listened to...
The voice of the heart is what I choose to guide me.  A lot of my ambitions are
founded by fear and greed.  I am not very good at them because there is a missing piece of myself
which cannot allow me to thrive in these areas.  I can force myself to do certain things even for some great
time; my mind is very strong and persuasive.  However far I get I am always yearning for a path of lesser resistance.
Resistance from the external is natural and to be expected, yet the resistance from within is what keeps me stranded
and unfulfilled.  I declare my surrender to my heart.  I declare that I will follow my calling which is
guided not by money, success, fame or any other hollow leisure and only truth, freedom, and authenticity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My heart and my soul are the guide for me.  And I will be here as a lighthouse to guide others in their journey,
if they so choose and wish.  I release myself from the shackles of victim consciousness.  I release myself from the anxiety,
the worry, the desire, and the games of cat and mouse with my ego.  I resolve myself from regret, and fear of choosing wrong.
I can walk with faith along a path projected by my highest self.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Into the light I will follow; leading my way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What this means is taking the hints from my soul when it knows what to do and actually acting out
the instructions.  For instance, I just got the hint that it is time to go to bed.  Instead of
prolonging my bed-time and procrastinating by continued web-surfing, I will take the action to go to bed...
So, good night :) &lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What skills should I be working on?]]></title><description><![CDATA[How do I want/intend to live my life?  I intend to live my life
comfortably, pleasurably, motivated by love, and doing things that
give me…]]></description><link>https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/what-skills-should-i-be-working-on</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/what-skills-should-i-be-working-on</guid><category><![CDATA[Reflections]]></category><category><![CDATA[Growth]]></category><category><![CDATA[Earth Star]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Mongiello]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;How do I want/intend to live my life?  I intend to live my life
comfortably, pleasurably, motivated by love, and doing things that
give me satisfaction.  Living from a beautiful, bountiful, abundant state of mind.
I like feeling complete.  There are areas of my life that I feel are not complete.
I find pleasure and fulfillment from working towards completion.  I recognize
an impulsiveness that can often take away/distract me from completion.  I also notice
food/taking snack breaks as a method/manifestation of this tendancy.  When I get
close or have the opportunity to be with my self, the best thing I can do is to sit with, listen to,
reflect on, write about, and/or learn from whatever is here.  I have been feeling incomplete &amp;#x26; detached
because I have not been spending time with my self when the perfect opportunities arise.
I am the keys to my own success, I am the answers to all the seemingly tough questions.  I am the roadmap through life&apos;s
journey. I am exactly what I want, and the best skill to be improving is being me;
following my dreams, my passions, my interests, my truths, and my desires.  Everything else is an illusion.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Morning Routine]]></title><description><![CDATA[Starting a new day.  Meditation & journaling is how i intend to start every day.
Getting the pinpoint accuracy of what my targets; Letting…]]></description><link>https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/morning-routine</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/KevinMongiello/kevinsblog/morning-routine</guid><category><![CDATA[Life Organization]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Mongiello]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Starting a new day.  Meditation &amp;#x26; journaling is how i intend to start every day.
Getting the pinpoint accuracy of what my targets; Letting go of any stressors.
Taking some itme to figure out what I want to say to myself.  Who I am today, what is present for me.
If there is anything I&apos;d like to focus on or know about my condition today, etc.
I usually get really bored with morning routines, and this is a good way to really spice it up.
I can write anything &amp;#x26; I am just giving space for everything/anything to develop, instead of the same motions every monring.
I can tap into the infinite to start my day.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>